http://www.oldwestburygardens.org/privacypolicy

Contact Us
Privacy Policy (click title to view privacy policies) Purpose of this Notice
This privacy notice explains our approach to any personal information that you might supply to us (or that might be collected from you) in connection with your use of Old Westbury Gardens (“OWG” or “the Gardens”) and sets out your rights in respect of OWG processing of your personal information.
This privacy notice will inform you how you can verify which of your personal information is collected by us through OWG web site and how you can request that we delete, update or transfer it.
This privacy notice is intended to assist you in making informed decisions when using this website. Please take a moment to read and understand it.
Please also note that this privacy notice only applies to the use of personal information collected by us from your use of the this website and during your communications with us. It does not apply to personal information collected during your communications with third parties.
Types of Information Collected
OWG does not collect any personal information about individuals—such as names and postal or e-mail addresses—except when such information is knowingly provided to the Garden. Personal information might be obtained from online transactions such as purchases or membership subscriptions. Additionally, personal information may be transmitted as part of a form submission or in connection with other activities, services, or resources made available on our site. Any personal identification information retrieved by OWG must be voluntarily submitted by the user.
OWG Web site does collect some anonymous “non-personally identifiable” aggregate information about visitors automatically when pages on our Web site are requested through a browser. This information is used for statistical purposes and to help us monitor how guests navigate our site, allowing us to tailor our services for the majority of visitors. Non-personally identifiable information may refer to information about our visitors’ browsers, operating systems, Internet Service Providers, or other similar information.
OWG Web site collects Internet Protocol (IP) addresses as a component of the non-personally identifiable aggregate information. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you’re on the Internet. This information is used only for non-user-specific purposes such as determining how many users visited a specific area of our site. This personal information allows us to deliver more helpful information, services and tools.
Such information could, if necessary, be used to identify a user in order to comply with safety and/or security issues or with legal requirements.
We may collect through our use of cookies, pixels, beacons, log files and other technologies personal information regarding your mobile device, computer hardware and software used to access the Garden Web site. This may include the following:
·
IP address of device(s) used;
·
browser type;
·
operating system and device type;
·
approximate location (e.g. New York City);
·
access times and dates; and
·
referring website addresses
How Do We Obtain Your Consent
Where use of your personal information by us requires your consent, you can provide such consent at the time we collect your personal information following the instructions provided; or by informing OWG by e-mail using the contact details set out in this privacy notice.
With Whom Information is Shared
OWG does not share personal information with
third parties.
How long do we keep your personal information for?
We keep your personal information only for as long as necessary to fulfil the purpose it was collected for, where we need to in relation to proving legal relationships or to comply with any of our legal obligations.
Access to Your Information
OWG retains user information in our secure databases. If you would like to access, transfer, review, or correction of or to your Personal Information, or to request that it be deleted or restricted in use, please contact us or update your preferences.
Confidentiality and security of your personal information
We are committed to keeping the personal information you provide us secure and we will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration.
We have implemented information security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal information that we have under our control from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification; and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.
All our employees and data processors (i.e. those who process your personal information on our behalf, for the purposes listed above), who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of the personal information of all users of the Garden.
Security
OWG protects all personally and non-personally identifiable information that it receives via the Internet against unauthorized access.
In addition, OWG Web site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to process purchases made on its online store and ticketing systems. By using this technology, online customers can feel confident that their personal information is protected from interception by any third party. Sensitive credit card information is not permanently stored on any of OWG Web server and though your order information is retained for our records, this information is never shared with other companies or persons.
What is a secure connection?
When a secure connection is established between your browser and a Web site, any data that is transferred over the connection will be encrypted to prevent it from being viewed by a third party. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, the standard for most browsers and servers, makes it very difficult for anyone to intercept or decode messages exchanged over this type of secure connection.
Browsers such as Netscape Communicator and Internet Explorer display an image of a locked padlock in their status bar when connected to a secure site. Secure transactions are also indicated when the prefix in the location bar of your browser switches from http:// to https://. If you do not see the padlock at the bottom of your browser’s window, if the padlock is unlocked, or if the protocol in the location bar is not listed as https://, then any data exchanged with the Web site is potentially visible to others.
Depending on your browser, you may be able to view authentication information about a secure page by double-clicking on the locked padlock in the status bar. For more information on how your software establishes a secure connection, see the help files for your particular browser.
Sensitive credit card information related to ticket purchases is stored in an encrypted database on a secure server. For other transactions with OWG, credit card information is not permanently stored on any Web server and though your order information is retained for our records, this information is never shared with other companies or persons.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your browser from a Web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can’t read data from your hard disk or read cookie files that were created by other sites—the Web site that creates a cookie is the only one a browser will permit to access it.
Examples of ways in which the Garden might use cookies would be to control access to certain user features, location beacons, log files, to customize content areas, or to analyze site activity and user behavior. OWG also reserves the right to use cookies in the future in conjunction with new content or extended functionality.
If you are concerned about the use of cookies, OWG suggests that you explore your browser’s options to notify you whenever a cookie is set, or to disallow cookies altogether. Users should be aware, however, that prohibiting the use of cookies may restrict the user’s access to certain types of content or features.
Links to Other Sites
Users may find content on the OWG’s site that links to the sites and services of our partners, sponsors, or other third parties. In many cases, these links represent cooperative projects or are established with persons or entities that have a significant connection to or relationship with our site. Although every effort is made to ensure that any referrals are to reputable and relevant sources, OWG does not control the content or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy at all. The Garden maintains a policy against the non-consensual collection or sharing of personal information and encourages visitors to review the privacy policies of any sites they visit to ensure their personal information is being protected.
Policy Changes
Occasional changes may be made to this document as new services and content are added to our site or to reflect changes in OWG policies. Visitors to OWG Web site are encouraged to check this document periodically to stay informed of current privacy guidelines.
Acceptance of Terms
By using OWG Web site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of OWG site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.
© Copyright 2020 — Old Westbury Gardens 71 Old Westbury Road, Old Westbury, NY, 11568
info@oldwestburygardens.org (516) 333-0048
Old Westbury Gardens
71 Old Westbury Road,
Old Westbury, NY, 11568,
Sign up with your email address to receive news and updates.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
